mpogd.com 2007-12-03

# Multiplayer Online Games Directory / Privacy Policy - Find Multiplayer Games Here

Play [**Games** ](http://www.marapets.com/arcade.php) at Marapets.| | | 

_This document was last updated December 27, 2001._

At MPOGD, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete MPOGD.com privacy statement.

**Collecting your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, rating games or posting to the forum. Personal information collected by MPOGD.com often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for four primary purposes: 

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once. 
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you. 

MPOGD.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MPOGD or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MPOGD, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MPOGD, its Web site, or the public.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, MPOGD.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
MPOGD.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where MPOGD, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

**Use of Cookies**  
To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, MPOGD.com collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the site.

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer’s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the MPOGD.com Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact [doug@mpogd.com](mailto:doug@mpogd.com)

**Changes to this Statement**  
MPOGD.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, MPOGD.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

**Contact Information**  
MPOGD welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by [e-mail](mailto:doug@mpogd.com), or postal mail.

| | |
